Register of the Russia. Posol'stvo (U.S.) Records, 1897-1947.
Hoover Institution Archives
- Naval Agent Office File, 1897-1920.
  - General (Box 265)
    - Correspondence
      - General
        - Outgoing
          - 1899 (Folder 5)
          - 1900 (Box 276, Folder 1)
            Available on microfilm reel 330
          - 1900-1901 (Folder 2)
            Available on microfilm reel 331
          - 1901 (Box 277, Folder 1)
          - 1901-1902 (Folder 2)
            Available on microfilm reel 332
          - 1902 (Box 278, Folder 1)
          - 1902-1903 (Folder 2)
            Available on microfilm reel 333
          - 1903-1904 (Box 279, Folder 1)
          - 1904 (Folder 2)
            Available on microfilm reel 334
          - 1905-1906 (Box 280, Folder 1)
          - 1906
            - May-October (Folder 2-3)
            - October-December (Box 281, Folder 1)
              Available on microfilm reel 335
          - 1907 (Folder 2)
            Available on microfilm reel 336
          - 1907-1908 (Box 282, Folder 1)
          - 1908
            - January-March (Folder 2)
            - March-October (Box 283, Folder 1)
              Available on microfilm reel 337
          - 1908-1909 (Folder 2)
          - 1909 (Folder 3)
          - 1910 (Box 284, Folder 1)
            Available on microfilm reel 338
          - 1910-1911 (Folder 2)
          - 1911-1913 (Folder 3)
            Available on microfilm reel 339
          - 1913-1914 (Box 285, Folder 1)
      - Financial agent (Folder 2)
        Available on microfilm reel 340
      - Melville, George Wallace, Admiral (Folder 3)
      - Russian Imperial Ministry of Marine
        - General
          - 1901
            - June-July (Folder 4)
            - August-December (Folder 5)
          - 1902 (Folder 6)
          - 1903 (Folder 7-8)
          - 1904 (Box 286, Folder 1-2)
          - 1906 (Folder 3-4)
            Available on microfilm reel 341
          - 1907 (Folder 5-6)
          - 1908 (Folder 7)
          - 1909 (Box 287)
            - May-November (Folder 1)
            - March-July (Folder 2)
            - June-December (Folder 3)
              Available on microfilm reel 342
          - 1909-1910 (Folder 4)
          - 1910 (Folder 5-6)
          - 1910-1911 (Folder 7)
          - 1911
            - January-March (Folder 8)
            - March-May (Box 288, Folder 1)
            - June-December (Folder 2)
          - 1912
            - January-December (Folder 3)
            - March-December (Folder 4)
              Available on microfilm reel 343
          - 1913 (Folder 5)
          - 1914 (Folder 6)
          - 1915 (Folder 7)
        - Main Administration of Shipbuilding and Supplies
          - 1901
            - January-October (Folder 8)
            - April-November (Folder 9)
          - 1903 (Folder 10)
        - Main Naval Staff (Box 289)
          - General
            - 1902
              - January-May (Folder 1)
              - June-July (Folder 2)
                Available on microfilm reel 344
              - August-December (Folder 3)
            - 1903 (Folder 4-5)
            - 1906 (Folder 6)
            - 1909 (Folder 7)
            - 1911 (Folder 8)
          - Secret
            - 1901-1907 (Folder 9-10)
              Available on microfilm reel 345
            - 1912 (Folder 11)
      - United States Department of Navy (Folder 12)
    - Financial records (Box 290)
      - 1899-1900 (Folder 1)
      - 1901 (Folder 2)
      - 1903-1905
        - Account book (Folder 3)
        - Report (Folder 4)
      - 1906-1907 (Folder 5)
      - 1906-1909 (Folder 6)
        Available on microfilm reel 346
      - 1907 (Folder 7)
  - American merchant marine (Folder 8)
  - Budget. (see also General/Financial records) (Box 291)
    - 1903 (Folder 1)
    - 1904 (Folder 2)
    - 1905 (Folder 3-4)
    - 1919 (Folder 5)
  - Commercial products
    - Armor plates
      - n.d. (Folder 6)
      - 1900 (Folder 7)
      - 1901 (Folder 8)
        Available on microfilm reel 347
      - 1902 (Box 292, Folder 1)
    - Bicycles (Folder 2)
    - Boilers (Folder 3)
    - Books (Folder 4)
    - Coal
      - 1900 (Folder 5)
        Available on microfilm reel 348
      - 1901 (Folder 6)
      - 1904 (Folder 7)
    - Corned beef (Folder 8)
    - Explosives (Folder 9)
    - Freighters. (see also Warships and freighters) (Folder 10)
    - Steam tubes (Folder 11)
    - Tractors (Folder 12)
    - Trucks--see Tractors
    - Warships
      - 1903 (Folder 13)
      - 1904 (Box 293, Folder 1)
      - 1905 (Folder 2)
      - 1909-1914 (Folder 3)
        Available on microfilm reel 349
    - Warships and freighters (Folder 4)
  - Conferences and meetings (Folder 5)
  - Diachkov, A. P., Captain -- business trip to South America (Folder 6)
  - Flint and Company, New York
    - Correspondence
      - General (Folder 7)
      - Secret (Folder 8)
    - Reports by secret agents (Box 294, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 350
  - Gerasimov, A., Lieutenant, Chertezhi k rukovodstvu: rel'sovaia podacha, elevatory dlia snariadov, zariadov i patronov i lebedki dlia elevatorov, St. Petersburg, 1903 (Folder 2)
  - Golitsyn, Dmitrii, Prince (Folder 3)
  - Hamburg American Line (Folder 4)
  - Ignat'ev, N., Lieutenant and Dul'skii, Lieutenant, Chertezhi k opisaniiu palubnykh ustanovok metallicheskogo zavoda dlia 6 dm. i 120 mm. pushek, Kronshtadt, 1910 (Folder 5)
  - Kent Machine Works (Folder 6)
  - Lidgerwood Manufacturing Company
    - 1901-1902 (Folder 7)
    - 1903 (Folder 8)
    - 1904 (Folder 9-11)
      Available on microfilm reels 350 and 351
  - Men'shikov, Iu., Second Lieutenant, "Radiotelegraph," 1917. Mimeograph (Box 295, Folder 1)
    Available on microfilm reel 351
  - Minorskii, N., Warrant Officer, "Ukazatel' uglovoi skorosti girometra i ego razvitie." Typed copy (Folder 2)
  - Musselius, R. V., Snariady i trubki avsrriiskoi i germanskoi polevoi artillerii, Petrograd, 1915 (Folder 3)
  - Naval forces and merchant marines. Printed matter, 1895-1906
    - France (Folder 4)
    - Germany (Folder 5)
    - Great Britain (Folder 6)
      Available on microfilm reel 352
    - Italy (Folder 7)
    - Norway--see Sweden and Norway
    - Sweden and Norway (Folder 8)
    - United States (Folder 9)
  - O'Kelly, Morris, Captain (Folder 10)
  - Port-Arthur's construction commission (Folder 11)
  - Retvizan and Variag, Warships (Folder 12)
  - Rodgai, Freighter (Folder 13)
  - Rozhdestvenskii, Admiral--see Russian Imperial Ministry of Marine/Composition and structure/1906
  - Russian Imperial Ministry of Marine
    - Commission for Compiling Instructions on How to Prepare Warships and Warship Formations for Battle
      - Board sessions
        - 1906 (Folder 14)
        - 1907 (Folder 15)
          Available on microfilm reel 353
        - 1908 (Box 296, Folder 1)
      - Subagencies
        - First Department
          - 1906-1907 (Folder 2)
          - 1907 (Folder 3)
          - 1907-1908 (Folder 4)
            Available on microfilm reel 354
          - 1908
            - February-April (Folder 5)
            - May-June (Folder 6)
        - Second Department (Folder 7)
        - Third Department (Folder 8)
    - Composition and structure (Box 297)
      - 1897-1989 (Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 355
      - 1905 (Folder 2)
      - 1906 (Folder 3-4)
      - 1907 (Folder 5-6)
      - 1908 (Folder 7)
      - 1909 (Folder 8-9)
      - 1911 (Folder 10)
        Available on microfilm reel 356
      - 1914 (Folder 11)
      - Naval agents abroad
        - Instructions (Folder 12)
        - Reports, Exemplary
          - General (Folder 13)
          - France (Folder 14)
          - Great Britain (Folder 15)
          - United States (Box 298, Folder 1)
      - Non-Commissioned Officers--see Officers and Non- Commissioned Officers
      - Officers and Non-Commissioned Officers (Folder 2)
      - Seamen (Folder 3)
    - Dolivo-Dobrovol'skii, Captain
      - Politicheskii element obstanovki na chernomorskom teatre, St. Petersburg, 1908 (Folder 4)
      - Strategicheskoe rassledovanie vzaimootnoshenii Anglii i Germanii, St. Petersburg, 1907 (Folder 5)
  - Scroggs, W. O., " Steamship Fuel Stations in Foreign Countries and Non-Contiguous United States Territories," Washington: Government Printing Office, 1919 (Folder 6)
  - South America--see Commercial products/Warships; and D'iachkov, A. P., Captain -- business trip to South America
  - Submarines
    - General (Folder 7)
      Available on microfilm reel 357
    - Clippings (Folder 8)
    - Reports (Folder 9)
  - United States
    - General (Folder 10)
    - Armed forces
      - Air force. Reports
        - Korvin-Krukovskii, Second Lieutenant (Folder 11)
        - Utgoft, Viktor, Second Lieutenant
          - 1919-1920 (Folder 12)
          - 1920 (Folder 13)
      - National Guard (Box 299, Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 358
      - Navy
        - General
          - 1909 (Folder 2)
          - 1910 (Folder 3)
        - Bases and ports
          - 1901 (Folder 4)
          - 1903 (Folder 5)
          - 1909-1914 (Folder 6)
          - 1920 (Folder 7)
        - Budget
          - Memorandum (Folder 8)
          - Reports (Folder 9)
        - Composition and structure
          - n.d. (Folder 10)
          - 1909-1911 (Folder 11)
            Available on microfilm reel 359
          - 1909-1914 (Folder 12)
          - 1917-1920 (Box 300, Folder 1)
        - Intelligence service (Folder 2)
        - Warships
          - 1909-1910 (Folder 3-4)
          - 1909-1911 (Folder 5)
          - 1909-1913 (Folder 6)
          - 1911 (Folder 7)
          - 1912 (Folder 8)
            Available on microfilm reel 360
          - 1912-1913 (Box 301, Folder 1)
          - 1917-1918 (Folder 2)
        - Weapons and equipment
          - 1903-1917 (Folder 3)
          - 1904-1914 (Folder 4)
          - 1910-1911 (Folder 5)
            Available on microfilm reel 361
          - 1917-1918 (Folder 6)
    - Economic conditions--see Foreign policy/General
    - Foreign Policy
      - General (Folder 7)
      - Mexico, toward (Folder 8)
  - Variag, Warship--see Retvizan and Variag
  - Vladivostok (Box 302, Folder 1)
  - William Cramp & Sons Ship and Engine Building Co., Philadelphia
    - 1898
      - April-June (Folder 2)
      - April-November (Folder 3)
    - 1898-1899 (Folder 4)
      Available on microfilm reel 362
    - 1899 (Box 303, Folder 1)
    - 1899-1900 (Folder 2)
    - 1900 (Folder 3)
      Available on microfilm reel 363
    - 1901 (Box 304, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 364
    - 1902 (Folder 2)
      Available on microfilm reel 365
    - 1903-1905 (Folder 3)
- Russian State Control Office File, 1917-1921.
  Available on microfilm reels 365-397
  Correspondence, delivery registers, financial records, minutes, printed matter, reports, arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - General (Box 305)
    - General
      - 1917-1920 (Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 366
      - 1919 (Folder 2)
      - 1919-1920 (Folder 3)
      - 1920 (Folder 4)
    - Correspondence
      - General
        - Letters
          - 1918-1919 (Folder 5)
          - 1920 (Folder 6)
        - Registers
          - Incoming
            - 1917-1918 (Folder 7)
              Available on microfilm reel 367
            - 1918-1919 (Folder 8)
          - Outgoing (Box 306)
            - 1917-1919 (Folder 1)
            - 1919-1921 (Folder 2)
      - Controller's Main Office, Petrograd, Omsk, Irkutsk, and Sebastopol
        - 1917-1919 (Folder 3)
        - 1919 (Folder 4)
        - 1920 (Folder 5)
    - Financial records
      - General
        - 1917-1918 (Folder 6)
        - 1918-1919 (Folder 7)
          Available on microfilm reel 368
        - 1918-1921 (Box 307, Folder 1)
      - Checkbooks and checkstubs (Folder 2-3)
      - Registers
        - Accounts (Folder 4-5)
        - Debtors (Box 308, Folder 1)
          Available on microfilm reel 369
    - List of files (Folder 2)
  - Anderson, V. Ia. (Folder 3)
  - Board sessions
    - Correspondence (Folder 4)
    - Minutes of resolutions
      - 1919-1920 (Folder 5)
      - 1920 (Folder 6)
      - 1921 (Folder 7)
    - Minutes of resolutions
      - 1919
        - May-July (Folder 8)
        - July-November (Folder 9)
      - 1919-1920 (Folder 10)
      - 1920
        - March (Folder 11)
        - April-October (Box 309, Folder 1)
          Available on microfilm reel 370
        - September-November (Folder 2)
        - October-December (Folder 3)
        - December (Folder 4)
  - Commission on Russian Freighters Returned by the United States Shipping Board (Folder 5)
  - Composition and structure
    - General
      - Correspondence
        - 1918 (Folder 6)
        - 1919-1920 (Folder 7)
          Available on microfilm reel 371
        - 1920 (Folder 8)
        - 1920-1921 (Folder 9)
        - 1920-1921 (Box 310, Folder 1)
      - Delivery registers
        - 1917-1918 (Folder 2)
        - 1919-1921 (Folder 3)
      - Reports (Folder 4)
    - Personnel
      - General (Folder 5)
      - Petropavlovskii, Vitalii (Folder 6)
    - Rules and regulations (Folder 7)
  - Consulates -- savings banks (Folder 8)
    Available on microfilm reel 372
  - Consulates -- savings banks (Box 311, Folder 1)
  - Division of Supplies
    - General
      - Contracts and agreements
        - 1919-1920 (Folder 2)
        - 1920-1921 (Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, 1918
        - May-August (Folder 4)
        - September-December (Folder 5)
          Available on microfilm reel 373
      - Supply orders (Folder 6-7)
      - Supply orders (Box 312, Folder 1-2)
        Available on microfilm reels 373 and 374
    - Advisory opinions
      - 1918
        - May (Folder 3)
          Available on microfilm reel 374
        - June (Folder 4)
        - July (Folder 5)
        - August (Folder 6)
        - September-October (Folder 7)
          Available on microfilm reel 375
        - November (Folder 8)
        - November-December (Box 313, Folder 1)
      - 1919
        - January-February (Folder 2)
        - March (Folder 3)
          Available on microfilm reel 376
        - March-April (Folder 4)
        - April-May (Folder 5)
        - May-June (Folder 6)
        - July-September (Folder 7)
        - September-October (Folder 8)
          Available on microfilm reel 377
        - November-December (Folder 9)
      - 1920 (Folder 10)
    - Audit. (see also Russian State Control Office File/ Financial Agent/Audit) (Box 314)
      - General
        - 1918-1919 (Folder 1)
        - 1919 (Folder 2)
        - 1919 (Folder 3)
          Available on microfilm reel 378
        - 1919-1920 (Folder 4)
      - Advance accounts (Folder 5-6)
    - Budget
      - 1918 (Folder 7)
      - 1919 (Box 315, Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 379
      - 1920 (Folder 2)
    - Commercial products
      - Appraisal (Folder 3-4)
      - Exchanges (Folder 5)
      - Shipment (Folder 6-7)
        Available on microfilm reel 380
      - Storage--see Shipment
    - Composition and structure. (see also Budget; and Russian State Control Office File/Russian Supply Committee/Subagencies/Financial Section/Rules and Regulations)
      - Correspondence (Folder 8)
      - Statutes (Folder 9)
    - Subagencies
      - Agricultural Section (Folder 10)
      - All-Russian Zemstvos and Cities Union. American Commission (Folder 11)
      - Anglo-Russian Subcommittee (Box 316, Folder 1-2)
      - Artillery Section. (see also Russian State Control Office File/Russian Supply Committee/ Artillery Commission) (Folder 3)
      - Central Military Industrial Committee (Folder 4)
      - Commission on Claims (Folder 5)
      - Financial Section
        - General
          - Correspondence (Folder 6-7)
          - Receipts (Folder 8-9)
          - Supply orders (Folder 10)
        - Audit (Folder 11)
          Available on microfilm reel 381
        - Credits. Receipts and registers (Folder 12-13)
        - Russian 5 1/2% war loan (Box 317, Folder 1)
        - Shumatov (Folder 2)
      - General Chancery
        - General
          - 1918 (Folder 3)
          - 1919 (Folder 4)
        - Advisory opinions (Folder 5)
        - Archives
          - 1918 (Folder 6-7)
          - 1919 (Folder 8)
        - Audit (Folder 9)
          Available on microfilm reel 382
      - General Section
        - Advisory Section
          - 1919 (Folder 10)
          - 1919-1920 (Folder 11-12)
          - 1920-1921 (Folder 13)
        - Archives
          - 1919 (Folder 14)
          - 1920 (Folder 15)
        - Audit. (see also Rogdai, Freighter) (Box 318)
          - 1919
            - May (Folder 1)
            - May-August (Folder 2)
            - June-December (Folder 3)
          - 1919-1920 (Folder 4)
          - 1920 (Folder 5)
        - Rogdai, Freighter
          - 1919 (Folder 6)
            Available on microfilm reel 383
          - 1919-1920 (Folder 7)
          - 1920 (Folder 8-9)
      - Information and Report Section (Folder 10)
      - Machinery Section--see Russian Remington Contract Rifle Trustee/General/1918-1919
      - Military Technical Section (Folder 11)
      - Mission of Ways of Communication (Box 319)
        - General
          - 1918
            - May-August (Folder 1-2)
            - June-November (Folder 3-4)
              Available on microfilm reels 383 and 384
          - 1918-1919 (Folder 5)
            Available on microfilm reel 384
          - 1919
            - January-February (Folder 6)
            - February-April (Folder 7)
            - April-May (Box 320, Folder 1)
            - May-July (Folder 2)
            - July-August (Folder 3)
            - September-October (Folder 4)
              Available on microfilm reel 385
            - November-December (Folder 5)
          - 1919-1920 (Folder 6)
          - 1920 (Folder 7)
        - American railway mission in Siberia, 1918- 1919 (Box 321, Folder 1)
        - Audit. (see also American railway mission in Siberia, 1918-1919) (Folder 2-7)
          Available on microfilm reels 385 and 386
        - Commercial products (Folder 8)
          Available on microfilm reel 386
      - Naval Section (Folder 9)
      - Russian Remington Contract Rifle Trustee (Box 322)
        - General
          - 1918-1919 (Folder 1)
            Available on microfilm reel 387
          - 1919 (Folder 2)
          - 1919-1920 (Folder 3)
          - 1920
            - March-October (Folder 4)
            - May-July (Folder 5)
        - Audit
          - 1919
            - August-October (Folder 6)
            - October-November (Folder 7)
            - November-December (Folder 8)
          - 1919-1920 (Folder 9)
            Available on microfilm reel 388
          - 1920 (Box 323)
            - February-May (Folder 1)
            - May-June (Folder 2)
            - June-September (Folder 3)
            - September-October (Folder 4)
        - Kizeval'ter, G. G. Correspondence and reports
          - 1919-1920 (Folder 5)
          - 1920 (Folder 6)
        - Representative of the Russian State Control at the Remington Arms Union Metallic Cartridge Company--see Kizeval'ter, G. G. Correspondence and reports
      - Transportation Commission (Folder 7)
        Available on microfilm reel 389
      - Transportation and Warehouse Section
        - General
          - 1918-1919 (Folder 8)
          - 1919
            - January-May (Folder 9)
            - February-March (Box 324, Folder 1)
            - April-June (Folder 2)
            - June-September (Folder 3)
          - 1919-1920 (Folder 4)
          - 1920 (Folder 5)
          - 1920-1921 (Folder 6)
        - Audit
          - General (Folder 7)
            Available on microfilm reel 390
          - Commercial agent (Folder 8)
  - Financial Agent (Box 325)
    - General (Folder 1)
    - Advisory opinions
      - 1920-1921 (Folder 2)
      - 1921 (Folder 3)
    - Archives (Folder 4)
    - Audit. (see also Remington Arms Union Metallic Cartridge Company)
      - General
        - 1920-1921 (Folder 5)
        - 1921
          - January-August (Folder 6)
          - August (Folder 7)
      - Mission of Ways of Communication (Folder 8)
    - Composition and structure (Folder 9)
      Available on microfilm reel 391
    - Remington Arms Union Metallic Cartridge Company
      - General
        - 1920-1921 (Folder 10-11)
        - 1921 (Folder 12)
      - Kizeval'ter, G. G. (see also Russian Remington Contract Rifle Trustee) (Box 326, Folder 1-2)
      - Russian Remington Contract Rifle Trustee (Folder 3-4)
    - Warehouses (Folder 5)
  - Naval Agent
    - General (Folder 6)
    - Rogdai, Freighter (Folder 7)
  - "Otchet o deiatel'nosti Russkogo zagotovitel'nogo komiteta v Amerike i ego Likvidatsionnoi komissii"--see Financial Agent/Advisory opinions/1921
  - Petrograd Zemstvos and Cities Regional Committee for Army Supply
    - 1918 (Folder 8)
    - 1918-1919 (Folder 9)
    - 1919 (Folder 10)
      Available on microfilm reel 392
  - Russia -- counterrevolutionary movements
    - General
      - 1919 (Folder 11)
      - 1919-1920 (Folder 12)
      - 1920 (Box 327, Folder 1)
      - 1920-1921 (Folder 2)
    - Commercial exchanges
      - Fur (Folder 3)
      - Hides, skins, wool (Folder 4)
    - Czechoslovak army--see Russian State Control Office File/Division of Supplies/Subagencies/Anglo-Russian Subcommittee
    - Kolchak, Aleksandr--see Russian State Control Office File/Division of Supplies/Subagencies/Anglo-Russian Subcommittee; and Russian State Control Office File/ Financial Agent/Remington Arms Union Metallic Cartridge Company/General/1920-1921
  - Russian gold--see Division of Supplies/Subagencies/Financial Section/General/Correspondence
  - Russian savings banks in the United States--see Consulates-- savings banks
  - Russian Supply Committee
    - General (Folder 5)
    - Board sessions
      - General (Folder 6)
      - Agenda (Folder 7)
        Available on microfilm reel 393
    - Budget, 1917
      - Report (Folder 8)
      - Explanatory note (Folder 9)
    - Structure. (see also Budget) (Folder 10)
    - Subagencies (Box 328)
      - Agricultural Department. (see also Russian State Control Office File/Division of Supplies/Sub- agencies/Artillery Section) (Folder 1)
      - All-Russian Zemstvos and Cities Union. American Commission (Folder 2)
      - Anglo-Russian Subcommittee (Folder 3)
      - Artillery Commission
        - 1917-1918 (Folder 4)
        - 1919-1920 (Folder 5)
      - Central Statistical Department
        - 1917-1918 (Folder 6)
        - 1918 (Folder 7)
      - Chancery
        - General (Folder 8)
        - Shumatov, L. A. (Folder 9)
      - Financial Department
        - General (Folder 10)
          Available on microfilm reel 394
        - Division of Supplies, Establishment of the (Folder 11)
      - Legal Department (Folder 12)
      - Machinery Department (Folder 13)
      - Military Agent (Folder 14)
      - Military Technical Department (Folder 15)
      - Mission of Ways of Communication
        - General (Folder 16)
        - Audit (Box 329)
          - General
            - 1918-1919 (Folder 1)
            - 1920 (Folder 2)
            - 1920-1921 (Folder 3)
          - American railway mission in Siberia (Folder 4)
        - Commercial exchanges (Folder 5)
        - Personnel
          - 1917 (Folder 6)
          - 1918 (Folder 7)
            Available on microfilm reel 395
      - Naval Department (Folder 8)
      - Russian Private Industry and Commerce Department (Folder 9)
      - Transportation Commission (Folder 10)
      - Transportation Department
        - Audit
          - General
            - 1917 (Folder 11)
            - 1917-1918 (Folder 12)
            - 1918 (Box 330)
              - May-October (Folder 1)
              - October (Folder 2)
              - November (Folder 3)
              - November-December (Folder 4)
            - 1918-1919 (Folder 5)